Guide to the Cornell clippings file, 1940-1989
Cornell clippings file, 1940-1989
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell clippings file, 1940-1989.
13-8-3367
Cornell University Library.
7 cubic ft.
News clippings, indedex cards
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Cornell related clippings from the Cornell Daily Sun, the Ithaca Journal, the Cornell Chronicle, and the Ithaca Times, organized by subject headings and including a card index.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Cornell related clippings from the Cornell Daily Sun, the Ithaca Journal, the Cornell Chronicle, and the Ithaca Times, organized by subject headings and including a card index.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University--Students.; Cornell University--Faculty.; Cornell University--Employees.; Cornell University--History.; Cornell University--Publicity.; Cornell University--Buildings.
Titles:
Cornell daily sun.; Cornell chronicle.; Ithaca journal (Ithaca, N.Y.: 1872).; Ithaca times.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
NOTES
See also Cornell University News Service records, #4-3-15: http://resolver.library.cornell.edu/cgi-bin/EADresolver?id=RMA00015.
CONTAINER LIST
- Series I. Subject Files
  - Academic Freedom, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Freedom, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Academic Skills, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Skills, 1977-1978 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Skills, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Academic Skills, 1983-1985 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Accidents, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Administration, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1959-1969 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1970-1976 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1982 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Administration, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Admissions And Applications, 1951-1975 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Advising System, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advising System, 1973-1976 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advising System, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advising System, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Advising System, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1952-1956 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1972 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1980-1982 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Agricultural Shows, Forums..., 1984-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1955-1965 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1966-1969 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1979-1984 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni And Alumni Association, 1986-1987 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Alumni University, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1970 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1980-1981 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Alumni University, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Archaeological Digs, 1959-1961 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Digs, 1962-1970 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Digs, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Archaeological Digs, 1984 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1959-1960 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1962-1964 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1966-1967 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1972-1975 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Arts, Creative & Performing, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1962 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1973-1978 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Athletes And Athletics, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Awards, University, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1980-1983 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards, University, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Students, 1948-1954 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Students, 1964-1988 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Faculty, 1950-1951 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Faculty, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Faculty, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Faculty, 1965-1976 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Awards & Fellowships-Faculty, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Beebe Lake, 1964-1965 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beebe Lake, 1972-1973 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beebe Lake, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beebe Lake, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beebe Lake, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Beebe Lake, 1986-1988 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - A Board of Trustees, 1967-1979 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - A Board of Trustees, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Board of Trustees-Open Meetings, 1979-1981 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees-Open Meetings, 1983-1986 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Board of Trustees-Open Meetings, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - A Board of Trustees-Board Study, 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1959 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1962-1968 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1974 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1977 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1982-1983 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Books (Written or Edited By Cornellians), 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1979-1980 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Bridges-Cornell University, 1987 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Budget, 1949-1979 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Budget- -1980, 1980-1988 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Buildings, 1953 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1978-1984 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Buildings-Growth, Expansion, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings-Growth, Expansion, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings-Growth, Expansion, 1977-1979 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings-Growth, Expansion, 1981 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings-Growth, Expansion, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Buildings, Growth, Expansion, 1949-1969 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Businesses- -Faculty Managed/Owned, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Businesses- -Faculty Managed/Owned, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1948 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1955 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1965-1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Businesses- - Student Managed/Owned, 1982-1988 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - Calendar, 1963 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Calendar, 1965-1968 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Calendar, 1970-1971 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Calendar, 1979-1988 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Campus Council, 1977-1981 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Campus Planning, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1972-1976 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1980 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1983-1984 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Campus Planning-Cranch Report, 1971-1973 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Centennial, 1963-1965 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - Central, Intelligence Agency & Cornell, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Central, Intelligence Agency & Cornell, 1976-1978 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Central, Intelligence Agency & Cornell, 1985 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - Charter, Cornell University, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Charter Day, April 27th 1965 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Chimes, 1955-1958 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1960-1961 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1973-1974 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1981-1984 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1986 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Chimes, 1988 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - Civil Rights Movement, 1964-1966 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Civil Liberties, 1967 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Civil Liberties, 1970-1978 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Civil Liberties, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Civil Liberties, 1986-888 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Commencement, 1968-1973 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Commencement, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Commencement, 1979-1985 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Commencement, 1987-1988 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - A Computer Facilities & Concerns, 1983-1988 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Cornell University- - History Presidents, 1949 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University- - History Presidents, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University- - History Presidents, 1962-1963 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University- - History Presidents, 1969-1970 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell University- - History Presidents, 1976-1977 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1949-1951 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1955-1956 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1962-1975 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1979-1985 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Daily Sun, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1975-1976 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1980-1981 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Cinema, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Cornell Federal Credit Union, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Cornell In Washington Program, 1983 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cornell In Washington Program, 1985-1986 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Cornell In Washington Program, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - A Cornell/Government Relations, 1982 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A Cornell/Government Relations, 1984 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - A Cornell/Government Relations, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Cornell University- - History- - Illustrations, 1907 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University- - History- - Illustrations, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Cornell University- - History- - Illustrations, 1906 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University- - History- - Illustrations, 1908 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Cornell University- - History- - Illustrations, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - A Cornell/Industry Relations, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - A Cornell/Industry Relations, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Cornell Initiative on African Development, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cornell Initiative on African Development, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cornell University History, 1980-1984 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cornell University History, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1964-1972 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1971-1977 (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1980-1982 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1983-1985 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Cornell/Ithaca Relations, 1985-1988 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Cornell/New York State Relations, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cornell/New York State Relations, 1971-1976 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cornell/New York State Relations, 1978-1988 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Cornell University-History, 1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University-History, 1948-1952 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University-History, 1954-1956 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University-History, 1962-1969 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Cornell University-History, 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1982-1983 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Corporate Requirements & Responsibility, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Crime At Cornell, 1982-1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Crime At Cornell, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crime At Cornell, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crime At Cornell, 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Crime At Cornell, 1979-1982 (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Day Care, 1972 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Care, 1974 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Care, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Care, 1979 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Care, 1982-1985 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Day Care, 1987-1988 (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Dean's List, 1963 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dean's List, 1967-1969 (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1970 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1973-1974 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1981-1983 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining-Coffee Shops, Sandwich Shops, Lunch Wagons, 1986 (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Dining Services, 1954 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dining Services, 1964-1983 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Dining Services, 1986-1988 (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1966-1968 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1976-1977 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1980-1983 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Racial)-Complaints Suits, Etc., 1985-1987 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1964 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1974 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1976 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1979-1983 (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Discrimination (Sexual)-Complaints, Suits, Etc., 1984-1988 (Box 2, Folder 26)
  - Dogs, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dogs, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dogs, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dogs, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Dogs, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 27)
  - Drug Use, 1949-1971 (Box 2, Folder 28)
  - Drug Use, 1972-1988 (Box 2, Folder 29)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1968-1969 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1971-1972 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1976-1979 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1985 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education- - Extramural, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 30)
  - Education-Graduate, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Education-Graduate, 1963-1973 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Education-Graduate, 1979-1984 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Education-Graduate, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 31)
  - Education-Undergraduate, 1949-1969 (Box 2, Folder 32)
  - Education-Undergraduate, 1970-1980 (Box 2, Folder 33)
  - Education- - Undergraduate, 1981-1988 (Box 2, Folder 34)
  - Emergencies, 1972-1973 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Emergencies, 1980 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Emergencies, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 35)
  - Employees, Academic, 1963-1973 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Employees, Academic, 1974-1988 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1970-1972 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1975-1976 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1978-1984 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees-Non-Academic, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1966-1967 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1972-1974 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1979-1981 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employees' Benefits, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Employment-Affirmative Action, 1970-1973 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Employment-Affirmative Action, 1975-1984 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Employment-Affirmative Action, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Energy, 1955 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Energy, 1966-1968 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Energy, 1973-1984 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Energy, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Enrollments and Dropouts, 1948-1974 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Enrollments and Dropouts, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments and Dropouts, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments and Dropouts, 1975-1985 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Enrollments and Dropouts, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Environment Research, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Environment Research, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Ethics, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1972-1978 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Ethics, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Exchange Programs, Academics, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exchange Programs, Academics, 1965-1966 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exchange Programs, Academics, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exchange Programs, Academics, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Exchange Programs, Academics, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Faculty- - Committees, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty- - Committees, 1965-1981 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty- - Committees, 1983-1986 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Faculty- - Committees, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Famous Cornellians, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Finances, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Finances, 1968-1988 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Financial Aid, 1948-1980 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Financial Aid, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Financial Aid, 1983-1985 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Financial Aid, 1986-1988 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Fraternities- -Discrimination, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fraternities- -Discrimination, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fraternities- -Discrimination, 1963-1968 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fraternities- -Discrimination, 1970 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Fraternities- -General & History, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fraternities- -General & History, 1981-1985 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fraternities- -General & History, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Fraternities- -Governance, 1960-1962 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fraternities- -Governance, 1964-1974 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fraternities- -Governance, 1978-1988 (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Fraternities- -Housing, 1963-1969 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fraternities- -Housing, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fraternities- -Housing, 1979-1980 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fraternities- -Housing, 1984-1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fraternities- -Housing, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1973 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Pros & Cons, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1961 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1965-1973 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1981 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Rushing & Pledging, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1972 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1975 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Fraternities- -Social & Charitable Activities, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Freshman Class, 1950 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1960 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1963-1964 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1967-1969 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1974-1975 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1977-1978 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1981-1982 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Freshman Class, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - Fund Raising, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1948-1949 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1952 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1962-1967 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1971-1972 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1975-1975 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising, 1978-1988 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1951 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1965-1972 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1985-1986 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fund Raising-Cornell Fund, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Fire Safety, 1967-1968 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fire Safety, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fire Safety, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fire Safety, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fire Safety, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - Fires - including Collegetown, Alt Heidelberg, 1962-1987 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Fires, Chi Psi, 1906-1956 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - Fires, Cornell Residential Club, 1967 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Gay People At Cornell, 1967-1970 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Gay People At Cornell, 1973-1975 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Gay People At Cornell, 1979-1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1947-1953 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1955-1956 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1959-1960 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1962-1970 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1983-1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Gifts, Grants, Trust Funds, Endowments, 1971-1982 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - Governance- -University Senate, 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Governance, 1976-1988 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Governance- -Constituent Assembly, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Governance- -Constituent Assembly, 1976 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Governance- -Constituent Assembly, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Governance- -Student Government, 1963-1968 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governance- -Student Government, 1980-1983 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governance- -Student Government, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governance- -Student Government, 1988 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Governance- -University Assembly, 1981-1988 (Box 4, Folder 3)